# **OMAR BARRAGAN**

Mexico | P: +52 2721194113 | obmoreno89@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/obmoreno89/ | https://obmoreno89.github.io/portafolio/ | https://github.com/obmoreno89

#### **ABOUT ME**

Frontend Developer (React.js) with 2 years of experience in web application development, I like to participate in new projects, in addition to contributing all the knowledge I have acquired in my academic training. I have the ability to work as a team, likewise I am in constant training to be able to propose efficient and permanent solutions. I consider myself a dynamic professional with great adaptability to new roles. Focused on creating clear codes and the ability to meet customer goals and needs.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

### **SYNCRONIK** | Mexico

Software Developer L1 | Apr 2022 – Actually

- I developed responsive user interfaces using HTML, CSS, Javascript, and React for websites and web apps, resulting in a 25% improvement in user experience.
- I designed implements and mockups provided by the design team, ensuring consistency of the user interface throughout the site or application.
- I worked closely with back-end developers to ensure proper integration and visualization of back-end data in the UI, resulting in a 20% decrease in integration errors.

### **HUBMINE** | Mexico

Frontend Developer Intern | Sep 2021 - Mar 2022

- I participated in the creation of attractive and efficient interfaces and user experiences for two projects using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and frameworks such as React.js.
- Continuously researched new technologies, frameworks and trends in frontend development to ensure that the site or application is always updated and aligned with the best practices of the sector, improving the efficiency and effectiveness of the team by 15%.
- Optimized website or web application performance to ensure fast loading times and smooth user experience, achieving a 50% reduction in loading times and improving user satisfaction.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Tailwind
- Figma

- Python
- Node.js
- MySql
- MongoDB
- Express

- React.js
- Redux
- SASS

#### **LANGUAGES**

- Native Spanish.
- English B1.

### **EDUCATION**

## UNIVERSIDAD ABIERTA Y A DISTANCIA DE MEXICO – UNADM | Mexico

Software Development Engineering Jan 2017 – Dec 2022

Degree work towards the study of software development.